Guide to the International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 66 Records WAG.010
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series IV: Shop Files, 1937-1979, 4
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company: the world's largest manufacturer and distributor of dental supplies, became a division of Pennwalt c. 1970. Representation case with full transcripts for engineers who want to leave the catchall unit represented by OPEIU/AFL Local 153. Contracts (including Pennwalt 1974), 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Company, 1953-1974 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co.: (see also Box 17 and 6/61) Unfair labor charge, 1955; IAM strike has 100% support of Local 66 members, 1959; members complain about business manager, 1979, 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - S.S. White Dental Manufacturing Co., 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Willcox Construction Company: (Queensview Houses) representation fight (Field Surveyors' Strike), 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - A.P. Williams Iron and Bronze Corp.: contracts, correspondence; bankruptcy in 1957, 1939-1957 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - A.P. Williams Iron and Bronze Corp., 1939-1957 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co. Representation fight: company holds captive meeting of employees and instigates an in-house union (Engineers Association), similar tactics of the Hollow Metal Employers Association. (Hollow Metal strike, 1957) Supreme Court rules in favor of Local 66 when company unilaterally raises wages to avoid bargaining, but compliance comes too late for the greatly reduced unit., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Williamsburg Steel Products Co., 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - World Steel Products Corp.: Company refuses to bargain (encounters are well documented, 1940-1942); wage increases, NWLB 1943-1945); contract lost through wartime attrition; representation sought in 1951 and 1956; bargaining delays again from company., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - World Steel Products Corp., 1940-1956 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contracts and agreements, 1946-1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contracts and agreements, 1946-1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contracts and agreements, 1946-1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contracts and agreements, 1946-1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contracts and agreements, 1946-1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contracts and agreements, 1946-1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contracts and agreements, 1946-1976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contracts and agreements, 1946-1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Contract negotiations and renewals; correspondence, 1974-1979 conference notes and employee data; joint committee correspondence with Lummus employees, 1950-1952; publications; clippings, 1967-1969; coordinated bargaining committee, 1979., 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 19/9], 1948-1969 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Joint Council of Unions at F/W Plants; correspondence and minutes, 1955-1959 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Joint Council of Unions at F/W Plants; correspondence and minutes, 1955-1959 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Joint Council of Unions at F/W Plants; correspondence and minutes, 1955-1959 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence; includes Local 105, Boston F/W plant (1953) (see also AFTE locals), Boilermaker's strike (1955-1956), resignations from union (1960, 1969-1971), and Wilkes-Barre plant (1977-1978)., 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Correspondence [see 19/34], 1950-1973 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Merit reviews; conference notes and employee data, 1949-1957 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Merit reviews; conference notes and employee data, 1949-1957 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Merit reviews; conference notes and employee data, 1949-1957 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Merit reviews; conference notes and employee data, 1949-1957 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Merit reviews; conference notes and employee data, 1949-1957 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Labor-management conferences, minutes, correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Labor-management conferences, minutes, correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Grievances; correspondence (seniority, layoffs...) Includes 1952-1953 compulsory retirement case, 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/3], 1946-1961 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Strike, flyers, clippings, notes, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Strike, flyers, clippings, notes, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: NLRB cases; correspondence, legal briefs: 1945 exclusion of senior employees from bargaining unit; 1955 grievance against two members who crossed picket line; 1961 certification campaign by independent union, 1945-1961 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/20], 1945-1961 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/20], 1945-1961 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/20], 1945-1961 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: [see 20/20], 1945-1961 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Wilkes-Barre plant: organizing and certification, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Retirement plan: agreements, drafts, Foster-Wheeler News, 1957-1967 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Retirement plan: agreements, drafts, Foster-Wheeler News, 1957-1967 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Lists: shop stewards, wage scales, personnel, seniority, 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Lists: shop stewards, wage scales, personnel, seniority, 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Lists: shop stewards, wage scales, personnel, seniority, 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Lists: shop stewards, wage scales, personnel, seniority, 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Lists: shop stewards, wage scales, personnel, seniority, 1950-1958 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Foster-Wheeler Corp.: Company publication: Annual report, 1957; Keating Engineer, Jan/Feb 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Contracts, 1937-1967 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Contracts, 1937-1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Contracts, 1937-1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Contracts, 1937-1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Negotiations: conference notes and correspondence., 1942-1967 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Correspondence: 1945-1947 postwar: layoffs, rehires for a new plant, scarcity of highly skilled draftsmen; 1952 minutes of special employees meetings 1954 - company executive v.p. is former union member; averting a contract strike; JLR on runaway shop in N. Dighton, Mass.; 1956-1958, new units of engineers are created for "methods" and "electronics". 1958 - growing labor-management hostility. (Discarded NY Times 2/28/60, engineering ads pp F 13-25); 1961- report of forced retirement issue; (1961 and 1963) "gripes" include charges of factionalism, problems with the business manager (before and after Raimist's resignation and the 1962 strike), one grouping allegedly influenced by a hostile chief draftsman (former union member); one-day walkout and 1964 reprimands to members accepting overtime., 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/19], 1945-1967 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Organizing campaigns (of white-collar and progress coordinators' units): elections lost. For other organizing see Correspondence (1954,57 - North Dighton, Mass.; 1956 - "methods", 1958 - Valley Stream), 1962 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/46], 1962 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/46], 1962 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - General Bronze Corporation: [see 21/46], 1962 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Grievances and arbitration cases, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - General Bronze Corporation: General data: company report, members data, profit-sharing, 1958-1968 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - General Bronze Corporation: General data: company report, members data, profit-sharing, 1958-1968 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - General Bronze Corporation: General data: company report, members data, profit-sharing, 1958-1968 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - General Bronze Corporation: General data: company report, members data, profit-sharing, 1958-1968 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - General Bronze Corporation: General data: company report, members data, profit-sharing, 1958-1968 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Dues check-off and seniority lists sampled, 1946-1961 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Dues check-off and seniority lists sampled, 1946-1961 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Dues check-off and seniority lists sampled, 1946-1961 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Dues check-off and seniority lists sampled, 1946-1961 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Dues check-off and seniority lists sampled, 1946-1961 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Dues check-off and seniority lists sampled, 1946-1961 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Dues check-off and seniority lists sampled, 1946-1961 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - General Bronze Corporation: Dues check-off and seniority lists sampled, 1946-1961 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - R. Hoe: Contracts, 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - R. Hoe: Contracts, 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - R. Hoe: Contracts, 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - R. Hoe: Contracts, 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - R. Hoe: Contracts, 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - R. Hoe: Negotiations, recognition/representation papers, conference notes and pay rates; 1958-1961- members' reports on field work and travel pay, 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - R. Hoe: [see 22/6], 1946-1968 (Box 22, Folder 18)